gpforums.co.nz 2019-03-01

# Gameplanet Privacy Policy

_This document was last updated on 17 October 2014._

Your privacy is taken seriously at Gameplanet. We will not give out personal information to any third parties whatsoever unless required to do so by law.

All information collected is used for our own purposes only and will not be disclosed to anyone outside our organisation. This covers all personal information including email addresses. We respect your privacy rights.

**1\. Use of Your Information**  
Gameplanet does not sell or rent your personal identification to third parties. We release account and other personal information only when we believe release is appropriate to: comply with law; enforce or apply our terms and conditions; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Gameplanet, our users, or others.

**2\. Email**  
It is the policy of Gameplanet to send our members email when using the web site, customary business communications (confirmation of registration, etc.) and occasional site updates. You may also be subscribed to our newsletter. It is our policy to immediately remove any member from any mailing lists upon the member's request.

**3\. Membership Registration**  
Our site's registration form requires you to provide us contact information and may also require demographic information. We may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company and our services. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

**4\. Updating Your Personal Information**  
Gameplanet provides you with ways in which you can alter your personal data, including changing your email address, password, etc.

**5\. Control of Your Password**  
You are responsible for all actions taken with your Gameplanet membership, email address and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your Gameplanet password to any third parties. If you choose to share your email address and password or your information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with this information and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy.

**6\. The Security of Your Information**  
We work diligently to protect the security of your personal information. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by ensuring you logoff when you have finished visiting Gameplanet using a shared computer.

**7\. Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use our web site. We use cookies to improve the member experience. We may also use cookies to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on many major web sites.

**8\. Other Information We Collect**  
We use additional information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Users who login have their IP addresses recorded. This information can be used to track users who abuse the Gameplanet system and will only be provided to legal authorities in cases of suspected fraud. IP addresses can be used, in conjunction with an Internet Service Provider, to find the internet account of a user and, ultimately, further information to identify a user.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on Gameplanet, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

**9\. Advertising and Third Party Links**  
Some Gameplanet advertisers may request information directly from users, or link to sites that do so. Gameplanet has no control over its advertisers' privacy policies, and encourages users to review such policies prior to submitting any personal information to them. Gameplanet contains non-advertising links to a variety of third party sites to enhance the member experience. Gameplanet has no control of either the content or privacy policies of such sites, nor should such links be considered an endorsement of these sites except where otherwise noted.

**10\. Updates to Our Information Practices**  
From time to time, we make changes to our information practices or alter the functionality of our web site. We always update this statement accordingly, so we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on privacy practices at Gameplanet.

* * *

If you have any questions, please [contact us](http://www.gameplanet.co.nz/contact/).
